Ganzorig Erdenebat

https://rozig.github.io

 $Email: the.ganzorig 25@gmail.com \\ Linked In: https://www.linked in.com/in/rozig/$

SUMMARY

Accomplished full-stack engineer with over 3 years of experience playing key role in system design, development, deployment and support of enterprise-level software. Strong technical skills, with hands-on experience in several popular web frameworks including Django, Flask, NodeJS and Angular. Personable team player with talent for collaborating with diverse technical teams. Skills developing REST APIs, integrating with third party APIs and microservice development. Strong SQL and ORM skills, experience with PostgreSQL, DjangoORM and SQLAlchemy. Expertise with Linux use and administration, experience with Docker and AWS.

EXPERIENCE

Genius Plaza Inc.

Miami, FL

Full-stack Developer

Aug. 2018 - Aug. 2019

Address: Alameda, CA

Mobile: +1 (312) 404-1266

- Microservice development: Worked on monolith system to microservice transition. Developed microservices and API gateways. Worked on database normalization to improve performance. Technologies used: Python/Django, PostgreSQL, Docker, AWS ECS, AWS RDS, AWS S3, AWS ELB, AWS ROUTE53, Jenkins.
- o **Genius Doctor**: Worked on web application development. Conducted unit and automated testing. Implemented CI/CD pipline throught Jenkins to AWS S3. Technologies used: JavaScript, React.js, Redux, AWS S3, AWS Cloud-Front, Jenkins.

Infinite Solutions LLC

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Jun. 2016 - Nov. 2017

Full-stack Developer

- o Mobicom Branded Application: Managed back-end server for Mobicom Branded Application. Performed back-end system, API services development, testing and maintenance and database design. Technologies used: Python/Django, MySQL, CentOS, JavaScript, Bootstrap.
- Golds Gym Website: Developed official website for Golds Gym Mongolia. Conducted unit testing and maintenance. Performed front-end and back-end development. Technologies used: Python/Django, MySQL, Debian, JavaScript.
- o ArigBank: In-charge of maintenance and front-end development. Technologies used: PHP, Angular.js.

Programming Skills

• Languages: Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bash, SQL SDLC: Agile/SCRUM, RUP, Waterfall

• Web/App Servers: Nginx, Apache2, Node

Frameworks: Django, Flask, NodeJS, Angular

• Web: React, Express, Webpack, Redux, CSS3/HTML5, jQuery, SASS Platforms: UNIX/Linux, MacOS

• Design Patterns: Strategy, Singleton, MVC

Web Services: REST, DjangoREST, GraphQL

• Tools: Git, Vim, Terminal, AWS, GCP, Bash, zsh

Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLAlchemy

Projects

- React.js boilerplate: Boilerplate project for React.js. Used webpack, styled-components and react-router.
- Online Publication Platform: Clone of Medium.com, built RESTful API and implemented JWT authentication.
- Mumagram: Instagram-like social networking web application for MUM students.
- MUMSched: Academic scheduling web application for MUM students.
- Online Banking Application: Web application that allows user to transfer money and manage their accounts.
- Nutrition Calculator: Nutrition calculator web application on Django (Python).
- Logistics System: Web application for cargo delivery on Django (Python).

EDUCATION

Maharishi University of Management

Master of Science in Computer Science; GPA: 3.90

Mongolian University of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering; GPA: 3.46

Fairfield, IA

Oct. 2017 - Present

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Aug. 2013 - Jan. 2017